<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Harvey Kandola</title>
    <link>https://harveykandola.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Harvey Kandola</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harveykandola.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Is About Values</title>
      <link>https://harveykandola.com/posts/marketing-is-about-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harveykandola.com/posts/marketing-is-about-values/</guid>
      <description>I recently came across a old video of Steve Jobs talking about building a powerful brand.

It&amp;rsquo;s hard not to talk about why our product is different and better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up in Silicon Valley</title>
      <link>https://harveykandola.com/posts/setting-up-in-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harveykandola.com/posts/setting-up-in-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>Couple of years ago, I moved my startup from London to San Francisco and learned a bunch of stuff along the way.
People have asked how/what/when and this post is an attempt to write down what I say in person.
We were early-stage and self-funded, hence the below reflected our needs, priorities and budgets at the time of the move.
Location After various scouting missions, it became apparent that you either setup base in Silicon Valley proper or downtown San Francisco (right or wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://harveykandola.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harveykandola.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m an old school Software Developer, CTO by trade, who gave up the rat race to build software startups. Have a passion for enterprise software, B2B, self-service bottom-up go-to-market models.
 Founder &amp;amp; CEO @ Documize Founded Countersoft  My pet theory at the moment is that a combination of open source core mixed with the Flyweel Model. can yield special results. Let&amp;rsquo;s see.
Thoughts herein represent my own personal views/opinions/ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>